George Kleine Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1886-1946 (Box 1-67)
  - The Great Train Robbery (Thirty Years Ago), 1925-1929, undated
  - Greater New York Film Rental Co., 1909-1915, 1928 See also Container 37, same heading
  - Green, W. E., 1917-1920, undated
  - The Green Cloak, 1923
  - Greene, Nelson L., 1928-1930
  - Griffith, D. W., 1909-1919
  - Griffith (D. W.), Inc. See Container 21, same heading
  - Gulick, W. M., 1929
  - Gunning, Wid, 1917 See also Container 64, Wid Gunning, Inc.
  - Guyon, Eugenie M., 1924
  - Haldenstein, I., 1929
  - The Half-Back, 1916-1917
  - Hallberg, J. H. See Container 61, same heading
  - Hampton, Benjamin B., 1916-1917, 1927
  - Hansen, O. L., 1926
  - Harcol Motion Picture Industries, 1926
  - Hardcastle, B. T. (Ted), 1920-1921
  - Harris, Sam H. (Officer 666 and Stop Thief), 1914-1920, undated
  - Hart, Frank W.
  - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 1928-1930
  - Hays, Will H. (Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America), 1922-1929, undated, (2 folders)
  - The Heart of the Hills (Girl From the East), 1915-1919
  - Historical file (Box 26)
    - General, 1900-1928
    - Clippings and printed matter, 1908-1930
    - Distribution, 1908-1910
    - Eastman Kodak Co. (contracts), 1909-1914
    - The Fly Pest, 1910
    - General Film Co. (financial statements), 1912-1917
    - Licensed exchanges, 1909-1910, undated
    - Motion Picture Patents Co., 1909-1913
    - Patent fight, 1908-1916, undated
    - Pathe News (15th anniversary dinner), 1925-1926
    - Publicity (Box 27)
      - Advertisements, [1900?]-1917, undated
      - Clippings, circa 1912-1928, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence and other items, 1914-1927
      - Quo Vadis?, The Last Days of Pompeii, and other films, 1912-1913
      - Show World, 1908
  - Historical Film Corp. of America See Container 21, same heading
  - Hodkinson, William W., 1913-1920 (Box 28)
  - Hoffberg (J. H.) Co. (list of films)
  - Hoffman, C. A., 1926
  - Hollis, A. P., 1924
  - Home Motion Picture Corp. of America
  - The Hope Diamond Mystery, 1919-1930
  - Hough (detective report), 1916
  - Houton, Alma, 1915
  - How Heroes Are Made, 1913
  - Howells (David P.), Inc., 1921
  - Hubbard, Elbert, II ( A Message to Garcia ), 1916-1926 See also Container 35, A Message to Garcia
  - Humphrey, Olgo (Mrs. Olgo Humphrey Hassan Broadwood), 1922, undated
  - Hunter, Thomas Hays, 1915-1916
  - Hutton, Clarence, and Mabel Waterbury, 1908-1910
  - Hymen, Arthur S., 1918-1920
  - Imperial Film Exchange See Container 33; and 37, same heading
  - Imperial Films (Clement-Mason Films [1922]), 1922-1923 See also Container 21, same heading
  - In at the Finish, 1917
  - International Health Board, 1920-1921
  - Inter-Ocean Film Corp ( The Unwritten Code, etc), 1922-1924 See also Container 62, The Unwritten Code
  - Italy, 1921-1922
  - Ivan Film Productions ( The Unchastened Woman and Conqured Hearts ), 1918-1920, undated
  - Jaques & Co., 1928-1930 (Box 29)
  - Jay & Dee Sign Service, 1930
  - Jefferson Pictures Corp., 1933
  - Jenner, William H., 1924-1929
  - Jennings, William A., 1917
  - Johnson, Ligon, 1924
  - Johnson, William A. (Motion Picture News), 1921-1929
  - Jones, Linick & Schaefer Co. Theatrical Enterprises, 1917
  - Julius Caesar, 1914-1930
  - Junk film, 1925-1929
  - Kalem Co., 1906-1927
  - Kane, Arthur S., 1915-1920
  - Kansas City Film Corp. See Container 18, Edwards, C. S.
  - Kay-Tee Exchange See Container 37, same heading
  - Kelley, W. R., 1922
  - Kelly, Kitty, 1918-1919
  - Kent, S. R., 1921
  - Kerman Films, 1927-1928
  - Kidnapped, 1916-1917
  - Kieran, J. M., 1928-1929
  - Kinetograph Co.
  - Kipling, Richard
  - Klaw, Marc. 1915
  - Kleine, George (Box 30)
    - Clippings, 1909-1928
    - European trips
      - 1913-1914
      - 1927, (3 folders)
    - Miscellaneous, 1907-1929
  - Kleine (George) Film Co., 1912-1913, 1918
  - Kleine (George) System, 1918-1919
  - Kleine Optical Co., 1908-1927 See also Container 21, same heading
  - Kleine Optical Co. v. Photoplay Co., 1917-1920
  - Klutho, H. J., 1920 (Box 31)
  - Knights of the Square Table, 1917-1923
  - Kosmik Films
    - File no. 1, 1919-1920
    - File no. 2, 1919-1924
    - File no. 3, 1920-1924
    - File no. 4, 1920
    - The Hope Diamond Mystery (contract), 1920-1921
  - Kyler, H. A. (Supreme Photoplay Corp.), 1920
  - Kyne, Peter B. ( The Hand-Shake Agreement, Light in Darkness, One Touch of Nature, and Salt of the Earth ), 1922-1930
  - Laemmle, Carl, 1908-1928, undated, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - The Lance of Kanana, 1917-1927
  - Laramie Amusement Co., 1915
  - Larkin, Harold, 1946
  - The Last Days of Pompeii (copyright), 1913
  - The Last Days of Pompei and Quo Vadis?, (Distribution in the United States ), 1913-1926
  - The Last of the Freight Thieves, 1919
  - Lauch, A. J., 1913-1922
  - Launching of the U.S.S. Salem at the Fore River Shipyards, Quincy, Mass., 27 July 1907
  - The Law of the North, 1918-1925
  - Lee, Henry (“Cyclo-Dramatica”), 1907-1908
  - Leibfreed, Edwin, 1920
  - Leslie, Amy, 1914-1927, undated
  - Lessor, Sol, 1919-1920
  - Liberty Film Exchange See Container 34, Magner, Nat A. (Box 33)
  - Licenses
  - Light in Darkness, 1917-1928
  - Lincoln and Parker Co., 1917-1919
  - Lion of Venice, 1913-1914
  - Literature and the Motion Picture, by Arthur Edwin Krows (galley of article)
  - Litigation
    - All Star Feature Distributors, 1915-1920
    - Bonds for various suits, 1917
    - Damage suits, 1916, 1928, 1940
    - General Film Co., 1917
    - Imperial Film Exchange, 1916
    - Kleine v. Schiller ( At Napoleon's Command ), 1913
    - Miscellaneous
    - Mudd & Colley Amusement Co., 1918-1919
    - Payne v. Kleine, 1914
    - Pirated films, 1920-1921
    - Smallwood case
    - Sturdo Amusement Co., 1918-1919
    - Turner and Dahnken, 1918-1921
    - Wolf, Nathan, and Morris Choynski, 1917
  - The Little Chevalier, 1917
  - Little Picture House See Container 22, same heading
  - Lloyd (Harold) Corp., 1923
  - Louisiana, Cooperative Extension Work in Agriculture and Home Economics See Container 41, same heading
  - Lubin, Sigmund, 1923-1924
  - Ludwig Film Exchange, 1920-1927 (Box 34)
  - Luporini Brothers, 1921-1922
  - Lynch, S. A., 1915
  - Magner, Nat A. (Liberty Film Exchange), 1919-1922
  - Magnetism and Electro-Magnets, 1920-1923
  - Major Film Inc. (E. J. Farrell), 1919-1920
  - Mann, Paul See Container 34, McCormick, Muriel
  - Massachusetts, Department of Education See Container 41, same heading
  - Mastbaum, Jules E. (Stanley Co. of America), 1917-1918, 1926
  - The Master Passion, 1916
  - The Matinee Girl (James Montgomery Flagg), 1923
  - Matre & Co. (Victor G. Matre), 1919-1920
  - Matters, Thomas H., Jr. See Container 61, same heading
  - McChesney, L. W., 1940
  - McCormick, Muriel, and Paul Mann, 1922-1923
  - McQuade, James A. (Moving Picture World), 1920-1921
  - Meille, Arturo (Tecno-Commercio-Film), 1918-1929
  - Melies, Paul, 1919-1920
  - Melville, Henry, 1914-1927 (Box 35)
  - A Message to Garcia (Thomas A. Edison, Inc.; Elbert Hubard II; Metro-Goldwyn Pictures Corp.), 1915-1925
  - Messing, A. H., and Alexander Yokel ( Quo Vadis? ), 1921-1922 See also Container 50, Messing & Yodel
  - Metric table
  - Metro-Goldwyn Pictures Corp. See same container, A Message to Garcia
  - Miami Studios, 1921
  - The Midnight Ride of Paul Revere, 1923-1924
  - Miles, Herbert, 1921
  - Miner Lithograph Co., 1914-1922
  - Minneapolis Film Corp., 1919
  - Minnesota State Board of Health, 1910
  - The Mishaps of Musty Suffer, 1916-1929
  - Montagu, Mr. And Mrs. E. H. (Box 36)
  - Montagu, Howard H., 1929
  - Motion Picture Chamber of Commerce of America, 1923
  - Motion Picture Club of New York, 1927-1930
  - Motion Picture Exhibitors League, 1916
  - Motion picture industry, 1914-1926
  - Motion Picture News, 1918, 1926 See also Container 29, Johnson, William A.
  - Motion Picture Patents Co. litigation
    - Annual summary of litigation, 1918
    - Bradenburgh v. Lubin, 1913
    - Chicago Film Exchange, Chicago, Ill., 1908-1918
    - Choynski, Morris, 1917
    - Damage suits, 1914-1918, (2 folders)
    - Expenses, 1910-1921
    - Globe film Exchange, 1917
    - Greater New York Film Rental Co., 1913-1917 (Box 37)
    - Imperial Film Exchange, 1910-1917
    - Infringements, 1909-1911
    - Irwin claim, 1918
    - Kay-Tee Exchange, 1911
    - Precedents, 1913
    - Preferred stockholders suit, 1913-1919
    - Roland, Richard A., 1913-1918
    - Sampliner case, 1916-1921
    - Scull, George F., 1916-1918
    - Smallwood case, 1917-1919
    - Swaab, Lewis M., 1916-1917
    - Texas suit, 1912-1914
    - Theatre Film Service Co., 1916
    - Travels, 1911-1913
    - United States Film Exchange, 1917
    - United States government, 1912-1919
    - United States Sherman law suit, 1916
    - United States suit appeal, 1916
    - Waters, Percival L., 1916-1919 See also Container 63, same heading
  - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America, 1930-1937 See also Container 25, Hays, Will H.
  - Moving Picture World, 1915-1917 See also Container 34, McQuade, James A.
  - Moyer, James A. (National University Extension Association), 1923
  - Mudd & Colley Amusement Co. See Container 33, same heading (Box 38)
  - Museum of Modern Art, New York, N.Y., 1935-1942
  - My Friend from India, 1920-1927
  - Myll, Louis, 1925
  - The Naked Truth, 1914-1927
  - National Academy of Visual Instruction See Container 41, same heading
  - National Association of the Motion Picture Industry, 1916-1918
  - National Association of Moving Picture Associations (William A. Brady), 1918
  - National Board of Review of Motion Pictures, 1923-1929
  - National Exchanges See Container 51, Savini Film Corp.
  - National Exploitation Co., 1923
  - National Non-Theatrical Motion Pictures, 1922 See also Container 41, same heading
  - National Republican Club, 1928-1930
  - National Republican Publicity Fund, 1921
  - National University Extension Association See Container 37, Moyer, James A.
  - Neumade, catalog, no.4
  - New England Educational Film Association
  - New Era Exchange, 1920
  - New Era Films, 1919-1922
  - New York Central Railroad Co. (Box 39)
  - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, 1929
  - New York Public Library, 1925-1936
  - New York Telephone Co., 1928-1930
  - Newgass, Nayfack & Waldheim, 1929
  - Non-theatrical films
    - General
      - 1909-1924, undated, (3 folders)
      - Printed matter
    - Amateur 16 mm film, 1927 (Box 40)
    - Carter (Katherine F.), Inc. (Educational and Motion Picture Entertainment Bureau), 1915
    - Crosby, W.C. (North Carolina State Department of Education and Carolina Film Corp.), 1921-1923
    - Distribution, 1922, 1925, 1928
    - Dudley, William H., and F. W. Reynolds, 1921-1923
    - Educational use of films, 1919-1922
    - Foreign, 1922
    - Industrial productions
    - Lectures, 1910-1912, undated
    - Lists of universities schools using films (Box 41)
    - Louisiana, Cooperative Extension Work in Agriculture and Home Economics, 1922
    - Massachusetts, Department of Education
    - National Academy of Visual Instruction, 1921, undated
    - National Non-Theatrical Motion Pictures, 1922
    - Publicity, 1910-1922
    - Questionnaire, 1927
    - References, 1910-1922
    - Reiss, Ernst, 1922
    - Sage (Russell) Foundation, 1922
    - Stock sales prospectus, 1923-1924
    - University catalogs, 1920-1927, (2 folders)
    - University engagements, 1922-1924
    - University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kans., 1921-1923
    - University of Utah, Salt Lake City, 1921-1922
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison, Wis., 1922-1927 (Box 42)
    - University propaganda, 1920-1923, undated, (2 folders)
    - Visual Instruction Association of New York City and National Academy of Visual Instruction, 1922, undated
  - North Carolina State Department of Education and Carolina Film Corp. See Container 40, Crosby, W. C.
  - O'Brian, Malevinsky & Driscoll, 1914-1924
  - Office furniture and equipment, 1916
  - Officer 666, 1912-1920
  - Okamoto & Co., 1922-1923 (Box 43)
  - Oldfield, George H., 1921
  - Othello, 1914
  - Pan American Union, 1922
  - Paper film, 1922, undated
  - Paramount Pictures
    - Famous Players-Lasky Corp., 1919-1929
    - Paramount Publix Corp., 1931-1932
  - Parker Pen Co., 1929
  - Parsons, Louella ( Morning Telegraph )
  - Pasquali & Co. (Spartacus), 1913
  - Patents
    - Edison, Thomas A. (edengraph), 1908-1911
    - Kleine, George (stereopticone), 1903-1906
    - Various, 1886-1926
  - Paterno, J., 1915
  - Pathe Freres Moving Pictures, 1911
  - Pathe News, 1925-1926
  - Pathescope, 1917
  - Pavlowska, Irene, 1925
  - Peckham, C. H., 1910
  - Pedrazzini, Guido (Unione Cinematografica Italiana), 1923-1924
  - Peerless Towel Supply Co., 1929
  - Peoples Amusement Co., 1917-1920
  - Perfection Pictures, 1917
  - Philip Kent in the Lower School, 1917
  - Photo-Drama Co. (Ill.), 1913-1925 (Box 44)
  - Photo-Drama Producing Co.
    - General, 1913-1917
    - Butteri claim, 1917-1920
    - Minutes of first meeting, 1914
    - Original charter, 1914
  - The Photoplay, by Professor Munisterberg (article)
  - Photoproducts, 1919-1920
  - Photo Products Export Co. (Box 45)
    - General, 1918-1925
    - Edison (Thomas A.), Inc., 1917-1922
    - Norway censors, 1919-1922
    - United Kingdom Exchange rates, 1920-1922
    - United Kingdom Photoplays, 1919-1922 See also Container 53, Sowerbutts, Alfred Henry, and Photo Products Export Co.
  - Photoprint studios
  - Pictorial clubs
  - Pictorial Film Library (Box 46)
  - The Pied Piper of Hamelin, 1919
  - Pierrot the Prodigal, 1914, 1916
  - Pilgrim's Progress, 1921-1926
  - Pirated films, 1918-1926 See also Container 33, same heading
  - Play House Co., 1918
  - The Politicians, 1925-1928
  - Pollitzer, Sigmund
  - Pope Leo XIII and Pope Benedict XV, 1946
  - Population census of cities in the United States over one thousand in 1920
  - Positype Corp. of America See Container 5, Bulkley, H. G.
  - Posters
  - Premises
    - Leases, 1916-1918
    - Rentals, 1919-1923
  - Preservation of films, 1924, undated
  - Press, 1917-1920
  - Price, J. L., 1922
  - Printing costs, 1911-1920
  - Prize fights (Johnson v. Ketchel and Johnson v. Jeffries), 1909-1927, (2 folders)
  - Proctor Automatic Projectors Co. (Box 47)
    - 1919-1929, undated, (3 folders)
    - Printed matter
  - Producers, 1920-1921
  - Producers Security Corp. See Container 24, Gradwell, Ricord
  - Production costs, 1917-1919
  - Production techniques (“talkies”), 1913, 1926
  - Production theory, 1922-1927
  - Prohibition, 1929-1930 (Box 48)
  - Projectors
    - 1910-1928, undated, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1922-1928, (2 folders)
  - Publicity, 1915-1921
  - Publix Theatres Corp., 1929
  - Putting the Bee in Herbert, 1917-1927
  - Quigley, Martin ( Garden of Allah, Mother, and The Warrior ), 1918-1921 (Box 49)
  - Quo Vadis?
    - Audit of accounts, 1913
    - Cash summaries, 1913
    - Contracts with Cines and James W. Davidson of Canada
    - Copyright, 1912-1921
    - First National Pictures and Unione Cinematographica Italiana, 1912-1929, (2 folders)
    - Messing & Yokel, 1920-1925 (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous, 1913-1924
  - Ramsaye, Terry, A Million and One Nights; a History of the Motion Picture (New York: Simon and Schuster, 1926 )
  - Randolph Film Corp. (liquidated shares), 1916 See also Container 24, Gloria's Romance; and Container 56, Tribune Co. and Randolph Film Corp.
  - Raw film stock (Eastman Kodak Co., etc.), 1909-1921
  - Raynor, W. E., 1929
  - Reiss, Ernst See Container 41, same heading
  - Rembusch, Frank J., 1922
  - Republic Distributing Corp. See Container 65, same heading
  - Republican Club, 1917
  - The Resurrection of Dan Packard, 1916-1917
  - Reynolds, F. W. See Container 40, Dudley, William H., and F. W. Reynolds
  - Richardson, F. H., 1923
  - The Ride of Paul Revere, 1929 (Box 51)
  - Riegel, Vernon, 1927-1931
  - Ritz-Carlton Hotel, 1924
  - Ritz-Carlton Pictures Corp., 1923
  - Roberts, May, 1929
  - Rockefeller Foundation
  - Rodgers, W. F., 1924-1925
  - Roebuck, A. C., 1925
  - Rogers, Rowland, 1924
  - Roland, Richard A. See Container 37, same heading
  - Romance (story rights), 1919
  - Rose & Paskus See Container 61, same heading
  - Rothacker, Watterson R., 1925
  - Rothapfel, S. L., 1916-1922
  - Rowland, E. W., 1923
  - Royal Film Agency, 1919-1921 See also Container 1, Albion Cinema Supplies Co. and Royal Film Agency
  - The Ruby of Kishmoor, 1917
  - Russian educational films (Amkino Corp.), 1930
  - S Film Supply Co., 1920-1924
  - Saenger Amusement Co., 1917-1921, (2 folders)
  - Safety Cable Co., 1929
  - Sage (Russell) Foundation See Container 41, same heading
  - St. Louis World's Fair, St. Louis, Mo., 1916
  - Sales, foreign, 1918-1928
  - Sanger and Jordan, 1915-1923
  - Saniel, S.
  - Saunders, Alfred H., 1921, 1929
  - Savini Film Corp. (National Exchanges), 1919-1922
  - The Scarlet Road, 1915
  - Scenarios, 1920-1922 (Box 52)
  - Schmidt, L. E., 1924
  - Schwab, Charles M., 1922-1927
  - Schwerin, Charles, 1918, 1927
  - Scott, Harry (Associated First National Pictures of Michigan), 1921
  - Scripts, 1911-1932
  - Scull, George F., 1909-1921 See also Container 37, same heading
  - Seabury, William Marston, 1917-1925
  - Seabury and Binder, 1924, undated
  - The Secret of the Seedless Prune, 1915
  - Secret Service, 1916-1926
  - Selig, William N. (Selig Polyscope Co.)
    - General, 1911-1930
    - Brown of Harvard, 1917-1920
  - Seligsberg, Lewis & Strouse, 1920
  - Serra, Guido, 1912-1925, undated See also Container 1, Alliance Trading Co., (2 folders)
  - Serra, Ugo, 1915-1916
  - Sheep's Clothing, 1919-1928
  - Sheridan, L. A., 1920 (Box 53)
  - Simplex projectors, 1915-1916
  - Singer, Paul, 1921
  - Slides, 1921-1930, undated
  - Sloane and Chase Manufacturing Co. See Container 61, same heading
  - Smallwood case (Ethel Grandin), 1915-1919 See also Container 33; and Container 37, same heading
  - Smith, Merle, 1920
  - Societa Anonima Ambrosio See Container 1, Ambrosio
  - Societe Generale des Cinematographes See Container 13, Eclipse (Société Générale des Cinématographes) and Urban Trading Co
  - Southern Enterprises (list of films for non-theatrical use), circa 1922
  - Southwestern Film Corp., 1919-1925
  - Sowerbutts, Alfred Henry, and Photo Products Export Co., 1919, 1922
  - Spartacus, 1913-1924
  - The Spendthrift, 1915-1930
  - Spitzer, Rorick & Co. See Container 63, Voris, William
  - Spoor, George K., 1923-1924
  - Spoor, Harry, 1919-1927
  - Square Deal film Corp., 1920-1921
  - Stahl Amusement Co., 1918-1925 (Box 54)
  - Standard Motion Picture Service, 1926 See also Container 64, Wilson, Eska
  - Stanley Co. of America, 1926, 1928 See also Container 34, Mastbaum, Jules E.
  - Star Safety Film catalog
  - The Star Spangled Banner, 1927
  - Starrett, W. A., 1928
  - Stars, 1916-1922
  - State University of Iowa, Iowa City, Iowa, 1928
  - Stationery samples, 1917
  - Statistics (production costs, distribution costs, etc.), 1917-1927, undated, (2 folders)
  - Steiner, William (Sky Eye), 1919
  - Sterling Service & Amusement Co., 1920-1921
  - Stevani, Mario, 1913-1914
  - Ste[venson?], Charles A., 1915
  - Stone, Harry S. (Film Sales Co.), 1920
  - Stop Thief, Who's Who in Society, The Commuters, and The Spendthrift, 1915
  - Storage vaults, 1917-1924
  - The Story That the Keg Told Me, 1917-1925
  - Straton, John Roach, 1922
  - Strehmenger, C.F., 1915
  - Strobridge Lithographing Co. See Container 10, Craerin, R G.
  - Studios, 1916-1920
  - Sturdo Amusement Co. See Container 33, same heading
  - Suicides, 1915, 1920
  - Supreme Photoplay Corp. See Container 31, Kyler, H.A.
  - Sussfeld, Lorsch, and Schimmel, 1908-1924
  - Swaab, Lewis M. See Container 37, same heading
  - Swanson, S. L., 1921 (Box 55)
  - Swanson Theatre Circuit, 1916
  - Syndicate Superfeatures, 1919-1920
  - Talbot, Charles H., 1928
  - Taxes, 1910-1925
  - Taylor Holmes Productions, 1920
  - Tecno-Commercio-Film See Container 34, Meille, Arturo
  - Teitel, Albert, 1926-1930, (3 folders)
  - Television, 1926
  - Texas Gulf Sulphur Co., 1931
  - Theaters (Box 56)
    - European, 1926-1929
    - Mergers and monopolies, 1912-1928
    - Programs
    - Projection and construction, 1914-1928
  - Theatre Film Service Co. See Container 37, same heading
  - Thefts
    - Panama and Canada, 1918, 1920
    - Taif, George W., 1919
  - Thirty Years Ago, 1919-1925
  - Thon, Frederick, 1930
  - Ticket machines, 1910-1915
  - Tiffany & Co., 1924-1925
  - Tilton, Benjamin T., 1929
  - Times-Picayune (New Orleans), 1917-1919
  - Tooney, Tom, 1925-1928
  - Town and Country Films, 1917-1919
  - Toyland Films, 1916
  - Trademarks, 1909-1918
  - Trade press, 1915-1927
  - Travel, 1916-1926
  - Tribune Co. and Randolph Film Corp., 1915-1916
  - Tri-State Film Exchange & Theater Supply Co., 1921
  - Trust prosecutions, 1927-1928
  - Tuohy, William H., 1925
  - Turner and Dahnken See Container 33, same heading
  - Tuttle, T. O., 1917-1926
  - Uber, J. E., 1927-1928 (Box 57)
  - Ullman, B. L., 1923-1925 See also Container 1, “Archaeology and Moving Pictures,” by B. L. Ullman, Art and Archaeology
  - The Unbeliever, 1918-1927
  - Under the Great Bear, 1916-1917
  - Union Trust Co. of Chicago, 1928
  - Unione Cinematografica Italiana See also Container 43, Pedrazzine, Guido; and Container 49, First National Pictures and Unione Cinematographica Italiana
  - United Artists Studios, 1923-1929, undated
  - United Cinema Co.
  - United Film Service, 1920, 1922 See also Container 63, Werren, Sam
  - United Kingdom Photoplays, 1924 See also Container 45, same heading
  - United Managers' Protective Association, 1916
  - United Projector and Film Corp., 1923
  - United States Bureau of Commercial Economics, 1923-1924
  - United States Congress, House of Representatives, Committee on Ways and Means, 1913-1918, (2 folders)
  - United States Congress, Senate
    - Bill for the prevention of block and blind booking of films, 1927-1928
    - Bill to codify, revise, and amend the laws relating to patents, 1912
    - Committee on Interstate Commerce, hearings on motion picture films, 1928
  - United States Consulate General, Italy, 1924-1925
  - United States Customs Service, 1911-1922
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1921-1930
  - United States Department of Interior, 1919-1924
  - United States Department of Justice, 1919, 1921
  - United States Department of Labor, Children's Bureau, 1920
  - United States Federal antitrust laws, 1914-1926 (Box 58)
  - United States Federal Trade Commission, 1915-1927
  - United States Film Exchange See Container 37, same heading
  - United States Government Printing Office, 1927
  - United States Library of Congress, Copyright Office, 1912-1940
  - United States Navy Motion Picture Exchange, 1919
  - United States Post Office, 1922-1929
  - United States Treasury Department, 1918-1921
  - United Theatre Equipment Corp. (Box 59)
    - Accounting, 1918-1926, undated
    - Arcus Ticket Co., 1923
    - Assets and liabilities, 1922-1923
    - Banking matters, 1920-1927, undated, (3 folders)
    - Bausch & Lomb Optical Co., 1923
    - Boetzel, Eric L., 1924
    - Calehuff, Charles A., 1921-1927 (Box 60)
    - Cifre, Joseph, 1923-1926
    - Cohen, Benjamin
      - Collections, 1926-1928
      - Collections in doubt, 1923-1926
      - Uncollectable accounts, 1922-1928
    - Contracts, 1916-1919
    - Coufal, Joseph F., 1923
    - Customers, 1923
    - Eckhardt, Conrad, 1923-1925
    - Edison Lamp Works, General Electric Co., 1923
    - Edwards, Herbert T., 1917-1927
    - Endorser's expenses, 1923-1928
    - Forms (Box 61)
    - Fulco Sales Co., 1922-1923
    - Graham and Scott, 1923-1926
    - Hallberg, J. H., 1917-1923
    - Inventory, 1917
    - Kleine memorandum, 1923
    - Legal papers, 1922-1926